chicnostalgia.com 2013-08-25

# Cocktail Dresses, Evening Dresses & Bridal Gowns by Chic Nostalgia - Privacy Policy - ChicNostalgia.com

**1\. PRIVACY**

Cstown Fashion Inc. (collectively, "us", "our" or "we") recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of all consumers who visit the website www.ChicNostalgia.com (the "Site"). All "personal information" that you give to us will be protected and kept confidential among CSTOWN FASHION INC. and its affiliated companies in accordance with the provisions set forth in this Privacy Policy. When we use the term "personal information" we mean any information that can be used to identify or contact a specific individual, such as a name, address, telephone number or e-mail address. With your permission, we may collect certain types of personal information in order to communicate with you regarding CSTOWN FASHION INC.-related products, services, promotional events or contests. This policy applies only to information collected by CSTOWN FASHION INC. via this Site and does not extend to any other website, whether or not it is affiliated or linked to this Site or to CSTOWN FASHION INC.. CSTOWN FASHION INC. does not intend to collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 years old. If we learn that a child under the age of 13 has provided personally identifiable information to the Site, we will promptly remove such information from the Site's files. If our practice changes, we will let you know by posting changes over the Site. Before any changes are made in how your personal information is used, we will give you an opportunity to opt-out.

**2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Identifiable personal information is collected when users voluntarily register with the Site or contact CSTOWN FASHION INC. via the Site in order to receive newsletters, new product launch information, special events information or to answer surveys, enter contests and receive notices of other promotional opportunities. CSTOWN FASHION INC. may also use the information you provide to create a personal customer profile in order to let you know of products, services or events that may be of special interest to you. Subject to the following paragraph, CSTOWN FASHION INC. will neither disclose nor sell any information about you to a party unaffiliated or unrelated to CSTOWN FASHION INC. except (i) to comply with applicable laws, regulations, subpoenas or court orders or otherwise respond to government inquiries, (ii) protect the rights or property of CSTOWN FASHION INC. or its affiliated or related entities or (iii) if CSTOWN FASHION INC. reasonably believes that you have used information from the Site in order to commit unlawful acts or acts that may endanger the health and/or safety of the public. CSTOWN FASHION INC. may appoint third party service providers to administer and/or operate certain functions or services relating to this Site or CSTOWN FASHION INC.'s operations and businesses, the proper performance of which may require a transfer of the information submitted by you. Any such transfer shall be under strict confidentiality and security obligations and for the sole purpose of the performance of those obligations. If you sign up to receive information from CSTOWN FASHION INC. but later decide that you no longer want to receive such, you may contact CSTOWN FASHION INC. at any time to cancel any option.

**3\. UNSOLICITED MATERIALS**

Through the Site, CSTOWN FASHION INC. requests that you provide certain types of information so that CSTOWN FASHION INC. may better serve you. The requested information may include questions and comments about CSTOWN FASHION INC. products, services or events. Please do not provide CSTOWN FASHION INC. with materials, including but not limited to business, advertising, creative, marketing or any other types of proposals, concepts, know-how, ideas and the like ("Unsolicited Materials"). All Unsolicited Materials that we receive will not be subject to this Privacy Policy. By submitting any Unsolicited Materials, you agree that CSTOWN FASHION INC. shall have the sole discretion as to how to utilize such Unsolicited Materials and you automatically provide to CSTOWN FASHION INC. a perpetual, royalty free license to use and exploit the Unsolicited Materials in any manner in its sole discretion. If any Unsolicited Materials that you provide to CSTOWN FASHION INC. are protected by third party copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights, you agree to indemnify CSTOWN FASHION INC. against any claims or actions brought against CSTOWN FASHION INC. relating to CSTOWN FASHION INC.'s use or possession of the Unsolicited Materials. CSTOWN FASHION INC. shall have no obligation to return any Unsolicited Materials received by CSTOWN FASHION INC..

**4\. USE OF COOKIES**

Cookies are pieces of information that any website may transfer to your browser that are then stored in your computer system. Cookies are returned to the website that deposited them when a visitor returns to that site. The deposit of cookies by the Site will allow CSTOWN FASHION INC. to save your preferences for your next visit. CSTOWN FASHION INC.'s cookies may also measure the general activity on the Site, which allows us to determine which areas and features are most popular. This information allows CSTOWN FASHION INC. to make improvements to our Site. Most web browsers are set up to accept cookies. You can, however, reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

**5\. SECURITY**

Protecting your information is of primary concern to CSTOWN FASHION INC.. CSTOWN FASHION INC. stores the information that it collects on a secure server. Notwithstanding the foregoing, no transmission of information over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It is possible that third parties not under the control of CSTOWN FASHION INC. may be able to access or intercept transmissions unlawfully. While CSTOWN FASHION INC. will use all reasonable attempts to keep your information secure, we cannot absolutely guarantee that security. Thus, any information that you transmit to us is at your own risk.

© CSTOWN FASHION INC., 2009-2013 All Rights Reserved.
